all right welcome to fix the world
Friday our live board meeting for
together tech where what is our first
project we're figuring out what we're
doing with the idea cafe
how we move forward with Gabey like how
um whoever done game piece over how we
move forward with how we can best
support game people and their projects
and together Tech and idea Cafe which is
our project and my project in your
project reasons for and at all of them
there's amazing projects within the
space of game B and I know I am I just
used the word struggling because I don't
know challenged with the tension of like
that everyone has their own project and
how amazing that is it at the same time
or can any of us do anything of everyone
has their own solution to right
narration of what that and there's like
competing ones which other people see is
benefit
I was talking to max Porter's yesterday
and he's like yes competition and profit
are good thing he said I'm like I don't
see it that way but I get why and I
think there's a benefit to competition
there's something that comes out of it
you don't want to say like you can't
create something better than what we
have anyway so sitting with just that
tension of what can I do in this space
what can together tech do what what is
decentralized with centralized what's
individual what's group all of it yeah I
haven't I haven't watched her did your
video talking about decentralized so I'm
excited to check that out in in yeah
that's it's a challenge I've had with
every project so I've been working with
I guess over the last five years with
different developers on different
projects and this other group I'm with
is the canonical debate lab so it's all
bunch of people coming together helping
people kind of argue more effectively or
communicate more effectively when they
have disagreements and it's for people
that have the same kind of goal post L
their own projects and we still can't
like set aside our vision to work on a
shared vision or their vision
it's really tough and I and I can't even
do it myself
so I can't I mean so I I think I'm gonna
really just trying to be helping
everyone out on their individual
projects and then which kind of what we
were discussing on Facebook and then
hopefully at some point they will start
kind of merging together where the
visions collide because actually Kylie's
vision sounded really close to together
Tech except not tech focus maybe I'm
getting curing Kylie except she's
Australian right she's the what I do
yeah yeah I know her screen was right
below you in the last video in the done
barn video and try practice Coria more
practice okay but I don't know that much
about it but it sounded like it kind of
this coming tackle something similar
yeah she talked about what she's doing
in the Omega rural not this last week
but the week before she gave us I think
a rundown maybe it was during the Dunbar
number one that we did she gave a
rundown to what she was doing and then
um a little bit more in the Omega group
but having I liked the idea the idea you
propose on Facebook I sorry I'm just
distracted because I'm trying to find
the the thing we did last week at the
very end where we posted the question
and people people responded just to have
it to refer to but that having people be
able to bring because I wanted to find
people who have project so we can have a
conversation so that we can build what
your is the difficulty that you're
talking about right that like we all
have our own vision we all have our own
needs our own challenges how do you work
together to have sovereignty and this
like leaderless group right like what
does a non hierarchical corporation look
like right because if we can't do it at
a micro level that's safe enough to fail
how do we hope to do it at a government
a national or even a citywide level
and but that was kind of we focused on
the question of like this is what we're
doing and why don't you want to be
involved I remember the exact questions
but which is good I got a lot out of
that I think it was a good structure to
ask like why what doesn't work about
this and of course part of its lack of
vision right like they don't see the
like that piece like us coming together
and figuring out the interpersonal
struggle the interpersonal struggle the
and then a project to work around is
maybe not quite what it was like people
which is what I've gotten a lot it's
like people either could help but don't
see the vision or they kind of would
like to be involved but they don't think
they're either they don't have the
capacity or the capability right which
capacity I get we only have so many
hours in a day but the capability it's
like do you want to help bring you to
the table that's enough your ideas and
there's a certain amount of my people
don't have the confidence to think that
their ideas and their they're smart
enough that they're good enough and I
get it because I went through that I'm
still going through that struggle I
think everyone that's life but like how
to get people over that but maybe it's
just not our job or my job in any way
it's like what people want to come
together be transparent but doing it in
the way that you suggested where we have
an idea cafe around other people's
projects that like I was like why don't
we just hold ideas cafes about idea cafe
about together tech and have them work
on our project what yours is better is
it's like yeah why I think then we can I
think one of the natural things would be
to do some of their projects first and
then do ours as one of those projects
yeah absolutely
one we've worked us on the kinks and two
it's more here is what's in it for you
right away right we're not like it also
feels like if we have asking people to
come be part of this we're asking them
to like get married before we even dated
right like it's like they're like wait I
don't even know what together Tec is and
like that's the point
the point isn't to come and like attach
yourself to it the point is to come and
figure out what it's about and grow it
together but if they have their own
project that they're just bringing to
the conversation of
how we can help them move forward right
one of their hurdles where does their
stumbling blocks what could we do
together it's gonna emerge much more
organically what we can do for one
another right as a meta group of people
with projects like what is the thing the
thing that would help us move forward in
our own projects and the bigger in my
mind's another project of creating the
tools that we all need without having to
put in money and time and trust into
each individual one in order to create
it so I like that idea now how do we
actually execute it I don't know if I
want to use so the one thing though is I
don't know if I want to use the Tuesday
space because the Tuesday space is like
the game B idea cafe what is because it
wouldn't really be an idea cafe first of
all would be on this channel because
it's not like I don't even know how we
do that like someone could give their
pitch and then we could each take five
minutes to give them a critique or
positives it's definitely a format yeah
and so one is that right like it's all
chicken-and-egg but like picking a
format and then trying it and saying how
did it work how did it work for the
group it's a crowd sourcing or
brainstorming and how did it work for
the person right like I love it when
people pick apart my idea like that is
like I love the debate piece that is
like where the energy is I enjoy it I
don't enjoy it for some reason people
pick apart pieces of it that aren't
actually about my project right like
people like capitalism work so like oh
it's cuz like my mission is so big of
like all of us doing this thing but I
forget that it starts small I don't need
to commit 7.5 billion I need to convince
or not even convince people already
convinced when they hear it right like
they know that the right people will
come on board at the right time we will
grow it organically and naturally in a
moment it's just my outie going things
they get that trigger but if people find
a pole in the in the thing and together
attack if it's like well this can't work
because that part I enjoy it's it's my
like running language of like them
critiquing something else and be
thinking and they're critiquing my
project if it's in direct critique of
the project I'm good I love it but other
people what I'm getting to is other
people don't necessarily right so like
what level are they looking for
as far as like when I hear someone's
project I want to pick it apart I want
to find out what how it runs right like
I want to be what if this happens what
if this happens and so yes what do you
envision it looking like as a beta right
like it the first like putting a collar
on bSpace and asking does anyone want or
we can reach out to hear a director is
not right there's the other one really
highly thank you I talk to her every
week Kylie and and say do you want to do
you want to do yeah where are they who
what channel are the omega videos are
they're being posted the omega videos
are posted on liber8 mankind's Eric's
same with that he did his own video
series I'm like I'll make a rule and
complex sources complicated and I'm not
seeing those my feet and I thought I
subscribed to him yell so like you might
not be public if they might be like
unlisted for us well that's true yeah
have you seen any of them I thought I
saw one yeah that's why I just played us
anyway so that was just the thought
because I'd like to see those of they
are public yes so yeah so I think we
need to determine kind of a format and
maybe even have some options in the
format depending on the person's willing
to you know a level of what level of of
contingent they want in their feedback
because it it you know it could just be
thinking kind of here's the pitch and
help me work on my pitch or pitch is
probably you know more of a game a term
but you know my ex how I'm explaining it
and stuff like that also you know ask
clarifying questions that will help work
on explaining it to people and then does
anyone have any resources or aware of
any similar projects that you know that
they should do so be information finding
and then ask people you know whether
they would help share and is there any
sort of non-committed you know well I
mean if anyone wants to commit
being on a project that's great but also
if there's some low low commitment sort
of ways to help so we kind of support
each other and say you know what we're
trying to do here build a community
build on this game be community to
support each other's projects and kind
of set that as the social norm I think
that Fitz can be principled so anyway
that sort of thing and then give an
option to say have the person who's
presenting talks or do they want to have
people kind of poke holes in it you know
what's their level of that because I
mean I've I've had quite a few ideas and
I guess two things one I've heard a lot
of holes poked in it and it is good
though that I need to find a way to
address those confusions at the
beginning right in the pitch head move
off although a lot of times it seems
like no matter how I and all the pitch
they're gonna have the question like I
can't cover like the all four things and
the pitch and so whichever one I missed
they're gonna they're gonna latch on and
and it's gonna be kind of hard to
explain but also being able to answer
that question quickly and efficiently
and practicing that and since we do rule
Omega if we're doing in the game B space
then them hoping us also craft that
response because they'll be listening
much more effectively than just every
people in the regular world I think it'd
be a great way to practice rule Omega 2
because we want them to come in and want
them to pull the information out of us
that we're having trouble expressing
right that's what royal mega is all
about so I think just as a way to
practice for practicing or Omega and
then getting the support on the on the
projects and having it feel like the
project's our community involved I think
would be great benefits and then yeah at
some point our projects will come in
although the more I'm thinking about
this I think my like recent score
project is will trigger game be people
in a negative way which i think is good
I think that like because the truth is
we're all approaching this from very
different ways and that is the diversity
that we need to be able to create it
like everyone's like that doesn't matter
this matters right like like currencies
the number one thing or the means of
production or political or forget all
that it's all about interpersonal miss
meditate and those all are needed it's
just in the Omega rule finding the
allowance for you do your thing I do my
thing and how do we support each other
in it and so I think that things like
raisin score although maybe not
themselves
uber game be right like it's more about
logic in the debate
it's like though that foundation of
information is still absolutely needed
because not everyone's gonna be getting
B and not like if you look it together
Tech org which is about to be up because
I'm meeting with the person this week
all of the stuff on there all of the
projects are intellectual projects
they're like the IMDB for politicians
and my brothers now working on and and
you know an education as an online
school and and all these kind of things
because that is the foundation of what
we need is a collective to be able to
move forward right like everything's
complex but if you have information and
we're having to define everything every
time and figuring out is climate change
even real before we tackle it that is
you don't even like you do your research
okay but it doesn't help if I haven't
done mine and it doesn't help if we
don't have a common pool to use right
and debate tools are important I don't
want to participate in debates that much
anymore I don't find them except the
muddle about my effect I'm just like
every they're very low value mm-hmm like
I'm gonna enjoy tearing other people
down a debate is a verbal debate is not
productive yeah yeah and so finding ways
to get the productive peace out of a
debate get the productive peace out of
just information right whatever you can
have that is black white or gray area
right make it very black and white that
it's gray area to have it be a bit of a
foundational like Wikipedia kind of is
right for like that and if one of the
number one places people go to you like
the Wikipedia article it's not owned by
us and there's clearly problems with it
but having something like that or like
look we tackle climate change not the
government not the scientists not we
said what was everything we needed to
know and then the enemy nor any of the
other versions that are out there having
a way to make more reason together
instead of one-off I have to learn
knowledge and debate you which is like
not gonna help because neither of us are
going to change our minds I just
realized that reason score is a
structured omega rule okay
not it doesn't cover everything but it's
similar to Omega rule and the fact that
you can't dismiss anyone's statement you
can't just ignore it it it affects the
score so you kind of have to discuss it
and the thing is you have is that it
encourages people to think deeply about
what people say and what they're really
saying and there's even a concept of
going in and editing their statement as
a group workshopping that statement to
be more and more clear I just huh that's
never all right except even if you can
actually go through again and look at
you're under that lens and be like how
does this become even more that because
that's what society needs is a way to
find the commonality in our debate right
the Omega rule how do you find them
that's signal in the noise and how do
you help anyone as someone who has a lot
of noise but a lot of really amazing
signal as well it's like I need that
help and I that was when we posted that
um last week on game B and Jordan I
think REE
rematch the question he was like I don't
understand it and we kind of unpacked it
a bit and then he redid what it was I
think and he was like okay I love it
like that's I don't have time to be
involved but like yeah I hope wish
people would be involved kind of thing
and
that is the kind of thing that I want to
help other people do for their projects
right like there was and then Chanel
talked about transparency that she
doesn't think like transparencies which
have gotten a lot of that isn't like you
can't be transparent all the time I'm
like I get that but it's about being
transparent about when you're not
transparent and creating it again from
the ground up is how do the if they're
you know how did the two of us be
transparent this is very transparent
we're live on YouTube I don't know how
we'd be more transparent than this
besides the financial information which
we will when that's a thing yeah there
is no financial information because
there's no money put in yet right so
when there's ten of us it's gonna be a
little bit harder but we can still you
know have a median or have like when
there's a record of it now that's not so
transparent if you're not gonna go
through it constantly so getting the
tags and the part that makes data usable
and understandable is to me what
transparency is it's like making sure
all information that is needed is
accessible to everybody and in a way
that's usable and understandable except
where that information being available
is going to be a detriment to someone or
the project itself in which case we're
transparent about the non transparency
and but that it's the same thing what
you said in the beginning like I can't
talk about all of it in a pitch cuz it's
like a tech cooperative and people don't
get the big vision of it so they're like
it's like with democracy and
transparency it it's like but wait we
demand democracy's not like those
problems of jamar of course there's
problems of transparency of course
that's for like creating it together
from the ground up of like what does it
look like to be transparent
what does it look to be democratic sorry
going back to the just that that like
what we asked on the game be space and
then having it having people work
shopping a little bit in in verbal which
doesn't work as well for me not verbal
sorry text room um is was still helpful
it was like okay yeah that's what we
weren't clear about and that's where
where I say when I posted that when I
had the conversation with black borders
I posted on the game be space that I
wanted to have a conversation about
decentralization because I keep being
triggered by the word because I think
they're attacking my project without
attack
my project right right and so I was like
I want someone who's passionate about it
we can have a conversation and Max
Fortis like why I wrote a book on it and
so he was willing to have a conversation
on video which was amazing but I
realized in the post I didn't I said a
chat but I need make clear I meant a
video chat right or a voice chat not a
because I'm like people are still
answering I'm like I'm not having it
it's not even a debate I can't really
have a conversation through text it's
too much to follow and responding to
people like no this is what I wanted I
wanted that the max borders or a group
conversation something about it
and I did I got it yeah at some point
I'll have it I have to have you look at
reason score to see if the way it
manages text is helpful to you your
neuro uniqueness or if it's worse so at
some point oh I want to have you take a
look and see if how uncomfortable it
makes you feel beautiful so I can sorry
I just hit my microphone again I will
kind of sit down I was thinking about
calling this kind of a project swarm you
know it's just a point where the
community comes to kind of looks at
someone's project and sees what they can
do to help so I'll kind of write up a
description and some suggestions and
then have you review it and then we'll
have to figure out a time to do it would
it be valuable enough to use this time
or do you think we want to have this
time to digest those times and just
create a problem I think it's probably
good to have this time to digest those
if we still want like together tech to
be the thing work I think this is
valuable in that regard where it's like
we're working on ours and and um showing
that write it like okay we have this and
we have this conversation now how do we
go did someone just comment and I just
want to talk about um so cube spawn
commented on which video could you
comment on keeps going better I think
the one that I did with max Porter's the
decentralization one he made a big
comment which I basically was like I'd
love to have a conversation with you
about your project and then I mentioned
what you had said in the Facebook that
we were gonna be I think I said crowd
sort
in other people's projects and I would
love to do that if with cube spawns
project as well either one on one
because I wouldn't want to understand it
better I think it's a cool I love Lego
it's like it looks to be like blocks of
Lego that are like you put together to
be a factory in my mind that's what it
is
and it reminds me of this is the TED
talk does it call the construction set
for a new society or something where it
was like building the the farm equipment
and a bakery and all the things you
would need to have a small village but
using interconnected parts which is
still I think a project but hasn't
really gotten the babies had a TED talk
they didn't necessarily get although
they would last time I check them out
which was a few months ago they had
moved forward with a lot of the
different machines and so was I point of
all this bringing that up um yeah about
cubes you thought might also be their
project whatever you just called it you
say projects form projects Horomia yeah
I like that I think maybe that sounds
like a swarm of projects as opposed to a
swarm of paper how PDI's yeah yeah I was
wondering whether swarm triggers people
harness uh but it's the idea of just
temporarily giving focus to a project
yeah so I'll workshop that some and send
you the description then we can maybe
discuss it and then I guess we'll have
to do another doodle poll to find a time
sounds good I am I mean I could I have
the Tuesday idea cafe which I still want
to do in the new year Wednesday I have
you make a roll with trial so the Monday
Verbeck e1 is the one of like okay Dodie
to participate in that one
so either Monday's or Thursday's or
possibly the other option is to use
Saturdays the one I do with my brother
actually could be for like that was kind
of division but to have people keep
coming back and brainstorm each other's
so having like equals four yet exactly I
mean it'd be a space
like one person comes and we workshop
their project right instead of a
pinochle setting one I think my brother
would probably be down with that but I
could ask him as well
or II I mean I don't want to do two
things I was like I could do that and
that any limiting have one but no too
much the Narnia this is like it's
already my head's time it's just when it
cuz the thing I'm gonna beat on Saturday
is also that other people are available
right not just that people who don't
have nine-to-five jobs or make alright
have the freedom to make more room
during their nine-to-five jobs yeah so
yeah so I'll workshop that and then
we'll see whether we want to maybe this
Saturday you can chat with your brother
and see if he'd be open to that or if he
wants to say focused on your partner's
sounds good and then if not we could
like I said Monday over Thursday do
either Monday or Thursday work for you
yes I can you generally make time on
either of those days okay because it is
that will be mean but this is for if
it's we don't do it on this Saturday
that means there's I can't even count
idea cafe this one and the one with my
brother if we have a fourth one it's for
ones that I'm participating in the I'm
also kind of hosting on one of my
channels so I can't really not be there
and how I'm sure we can figure out it
would not be there and have someone else
do it whereas the Omega rule I kind of
Ken right it's not online I do not
Erik's doing it so um yes I think I'd
rather it be on Saturday and have three
a week that are the ones that I have to
go do with right yeah cuz I was thinking
what are you gonna be doing a video
again every day that it will be pushing
here your social skills
fits in with that ones cause no local
stuff right I don't actually know who
that is or what you're talking about so
if it fits in for you yes
that's kind of my my understanding of
external knowledge now is like
everyone's supposed to bring their own
external knowledge to the table we're
not always supposed to go back and learn
the same things like everyone's just to
read the same books everyone's just
listen to the same lectures and then
which would honestly be amazing anyway
and then we'd be able to bring the
conversation but we can't there's too
much information out there
so to have all that information in being
able to bring bring people with diverse
information whether it's a little bit of
understanding or a lot of deep
understanding and just whatever you
bring to the table Truby I know what p2p
means
peer-to-peer I just got accepted by a
Facebook group that was called by that
name but I think that's used in pretty
much every that's all bit decentralized
yeah Marcin yeah I'm consistently
googling terms in the game be space and
people and I've just had to come to
terms that I'm not gonna understand half
of what's going on I think cuz I don't
know you can't know unless we create a
tool to make it easily understandable
right like who's talking to who and what
did they come up with like I you can't
listen to every you had even listed all
Jordan and Daniel stuff let alone yeah
these conversations and the Omega rule
that we're posting you like the idea
Cafe is like you can't watch them all
nor should you
the point is to participate where you
want to and then it would be nice to
have um to know to know what was talked
about and then the gist of it to have
that yeah game be key concept videos
that I can't remember his actual name
but liberate mankind's his YouTube
channel
those have been really helpful to me
because a couple of the ones I thought I
knew and I guess I did to some extent
but um it helped clarify some of the
nuances so yeah I kind of see in the
future it'd be nice to have something
expands on that I would also like to
work on a terminology that's less
obscure
like I think there's a better word for
Omega rule than I'll make a rule that
requires less education but I could be
rolling actually that one's pretty
complex to explain and a couple more in
an intuitive manner ya know even risk
participating like Star TV I'll make a
rule group and then once I was like okay
ever practice and make a roll is like
wait what's alpha rule if I wouldn't ask
the question on Facebook something I
can't find it anywhere
and you can't really do alpha without
Omega or make it without alpha it's like
finding the signal is one of them and
finding it like letting the noise go
it's like kind of the other one so it's
like you surrender on to signal what is
signal is one of them and render on to
noise what is know is this the other and
it's like yeah and so one of the
problems with that is that there's there
seems to be a lot of playful wording
that is also noise like render unto
that's noise in my signal would be you
know focus on the things that are
meaningful yeah and let go of the things
that are not providing value to the
other one you know so I just would like
to see a plane you know a planer
explained to me like I'm five sort of
description and one of my other side
projects is I bought term dot FYI
to start a new dictionary because in and
I'm just going off on my own projects
now by the way so this is going good but
in none of the dictionaries you can't
link to a specific definition you have
to link to a word so if I say this is
this is what I mean you then have to
tell them oh here go to this link and
then looked at definition five so it's
turned out fYI is just a page to where
it's you can go to a term and then you
could link to a specific definition and
that will be up top so that so that you
can wait when you're having a
conversation then at the end you could
just put you know Omega roll - meaning
the second definition of Omega roll not
the first one we did and gave me 10
years ago right would be I think would
be a helpful thing so just so you can
hyperlink to a see
definition instead of a whole word be
nice I mean no these are new Gabey
concepts that have to be workshop to
figure it out I like the idea of simple
language and like it explains you like
I'm a five-year-old
but having even in the game B space
right having like a game B list of lingo
and be able to link back to the main
website but also like to be able to live
or maybe you seen sovereignty
differently right than anyway
definitions that are out there so it's
like here's the game this is what we
talk women have baby in soccer me
however some of the people in game be
using in this context or this context
yeah that's a great point so for my term
dot fYI website I think I will that's I
think oh I had that to my list of things
to do is also have maybe the I don't
know if they're called ontology so if
that's the wrong term but yeah a list of
definitions that are tend to be used
within a certain context or a certain
group and that would have all the links
to all the words so people can in in the
specific ways they're used in this group
and maybe a little disambiguation like
when people think of sovereignty they
often mean they think of these five
things well we mean just this this one
are these two yeah so yeah that's that's
a really good idea I think I had that my
never-ending to-do list this might also
be something that is way too maybe the
whole world doesn't revolve around me
and everything that's it need to be so
it works for me but videos linking to
like the concept being explained right
like in the inside I make a rule having
Eric's video up there because it's the
best one that's available right now but
isn't Jordan and Daniel talking or
something right it's like here's the
actual or here's the point where Daniel
and Jordan talk about it right like
having all of the lists within that to
say here's how you can get deeper into
this topic but if it's just a definition
website that might be like that's a
different website that does that and
then they always do great together I
think that fits I think that would be
like a phase two yeah because I want to
have the definition but also yeah just
having links to other things and of
course the links could be videos would
be good videos or links and I also
wanted to have one one where it where if
you link to a certain definition like
we're using Omega rule it's going to
have
suggested alternatives so if there's
just a vague term that's you know that
maybe there's a clear way to say it
mm-hmm
but yeah add videos or links for further
reading keep spotting I forgot I looked
up your name your name is actually I
won't say your name because I don't know
if people want their actual name said
it's like liberate mankind versus Eric
but keep spawn I looked up your name so
I don't know your name kinda sorta cuz I
memories not great but um was I gonna
say
Oh beginning of your comment you had
said that you were like this is too
intellectual you're not actually doing
things and I'm kind of realizing that is
my role my role is to literally which
annoys the out of me when everyone else
does it like there's people who have
looked up to in the past like Robert
Kiyosaki why no longer look up to but
like I don't if you don't eat Rich Dad
Poor Dad he does business closely and so
it's like learn to do financial planning
okay in every book is the same this
four-quadrant like you work here you're
an entrepreneur you're here you're an
employee it's like teach people how to
actually learn financial language like
could you do one book to actually tell
people how to do the thing that you're
like not there's a ton of people who are
like this is how we could save the world
but they're just the intellectual piece
right there like this is what we need to
do um Richard Wolff is that the one
who's like worker cooperatives he's kind
of working towards doing them but he's
mainly just like no we need worker
cooperatives so maybe that is my rule
but like maybe it is just having the
conversations and because I know I can't
I can't code and I can't do that piece
of it but I can have a conversation and
that's what the idea Cafe is it's like
finding the doing in the conversation
like there's something there like
figuring that piece out yeah we all have
our different roles and value so our
values opponent right horn but yeah
different things we can contribute and
yeah that's the you know so you have the
passion you have the raw ideas and the
fortitude to have these schedule these
meetings or be in these meetings right
and post them you're a host for the
ideas so yes that's all great value but
it sounds like you're willing to get
down into the weeds a little bit more
than they are then what you were
complaining about the people that are
just kind of here's the broad idea go
for it yeah you're you're you're
comfortable with going one level deeper
like you know now let's create that
training on how to do financial literacy
right yeah step or link to it right so
which is it's like I can't do the actual
creation of the thing so I'm saying he's
wrong and not doing it but like at least
the idea of someone needs to do this and
here's the best one out there
I hate like right somebody that's my
role if I could have my dream job or
whatever position on this planet would
be like to just give ideas and somehow
they get made because I can't really
like following through like by the time
we're creating one website I have five
other ones I want to create I think
that's very common there's people who
are like idea people people who are poke
holes and things people and I'm both of
those people and then people who are
like get into it and actually do it and
there's people who want to break it down
right into tasks I can't be that person
that I can take on some of the tasks
like and I can sometimes break other
people's projects down for them into
tasks just not mine
it's like how do I make a meal I
couldn't possibly it's like look up a
recipe step one no I couldn't possibly
yeah too much executive functioning
alright so what are we we're good at I'm
talking about
you're gonna write up a thing for the
whatever we're gonna call the project
spawn spawning the wrong word swarming
and we'll put that in the game be space
full schedule one for the new year we
rented a pool a dutiful four times that
work yeah I mean or if you want to let
maybe talk to your brother and if you
want to just use Saturday then we won't
even give it's better not to give the
yeah we'll just give them all signal no
noise awesome and maybe I just can
figure it out for one day a week like 11
o'clock although it works because it
kind of works barely for people in
Australia people in in
you know Europe it doesn't really work
for me to have an 11:00 a.m.
conversation every day because like I
feel like I can't do anything before and
I can't let you anything after it and so
it kind of eats up the whole day right
so like having one the 9:00 a.m. one
works even those on Saturday or having
one it like - or sorry 1:32 like 2:30 so
I can still go pick up my kid from
school works as well um as long as it's
this like this one we're we're cutting
it off in an hour and not like and the
idea cafe is the same thing rather than
like the Omega rule or any of the other
where it's like you got to start a
conversation it's amazing so you just
let it go and go that I would need to
have it you know what I mean like here
or I can leave and everyone else can
continue work shopping which is totally
yeah just let me know think about it let
me know what time works for you I think
we'll just use that as a default and if
people that can't make it like that have
a project or something we can figure
those individual ones out and then I
host them you don't have to be there so
we could tag T pon that and just see how
it works but I think just throwing a
time out that's that works for us - yeah
yeah I know you host you might be
perfect cuz I'm like another bring it
back here I have so many things hosted
on this channel at the moment and it's
like is basically just that the
conversations but if they one on
Saturday becomes that one also it's much
more yeah on Saturday mornings have a
meeting with my brother about his
business ideas that I was helping him
with so it's very similar to what you're
doing with your brother it's kind of
funny although he just had a baby so
he's a little preoccupied
babies and then hopefully having our
first one of that will be in the new
year but we can probably figure out and
touch base with like people who've had
projects like he was fun and asked like
is this something you're into and just
posting that on your game face does
anyone have a project they would like to
workshop yes and also propose you know
my little write-up and just say you know
let's iterate on this if there's a if
there's better way to phrase it or if
there's better tasks or if there's a
better way to organize that conversation
then let us know I don't think they'll
have much feedback but it's worth giving
the option and then yeah who all wants
to be taken opportunity in the hot
see and that it like that it is about
you and your project so how hot do you
want it to be right do you want to smoke
holes in it do you don't want to poke
holes in it also just like in the idea
cafe which I completely oh wait I'm
getting better on it forget to be like
you don't have to share for five minutes
you can pass you can sit and listen and
just contribute when you want to write
that same like you can pass on a
question right this isn't an interview
like it's a if I ask you something to
poke a hole in and you don't want to
answer it doesn't feel comfortable I
don't you don't need to answer it right
not that it is or I don't know I will
figure that out or like throws back the
audience I don't know what do you think
yeah my solution I think the assumption
is that these would be recorded and
displayed rather than even happening in
discussion afterwards because one the
main point one of the main values of it
to the people doing the projects is that
it gets their project out there right so
absolutely if it's a game be appropriate
project will post on the game B site
after Facebook and post it on Twitter
afterwards if they think it you know
that'd be kind of the goal if it yeah
it's the game B sensibilities and maybe
I don't know if you're comfortable with
this um but just like after the edgy
cafe yeah we vote on whether or not
we're keeping it whether or not ready to
leave it that maybe instead of voting on
it cuz that seems weird that the person
right if it's your project and you feel
like it was a positive experience and
you're like yes I want that out there
right letting them kind of decide
whether it's out there or not and then
yeah that's that's perfect yeah they
should have an option say oh I just I'd
said it all wrong and everybody yeah I
just I just rather not confuse people by
having this out there but I'd be happy
to do it again with them offense you
know yeah exactly right and and also
maybe even revisit you know after you go
through the first thing revisit these
kind of projects that were you at what's
going on and stuff like that if we ever
know projects have a monthly project
sorry monthly meeting like have three
three weeks of doing people's workshop
being and then another one for everyone
who's been on can come on in to savor
they are and say if there's like a
little thing that they need right one
that's more yeah yeah yeah and that
really fits with with what you were
doing with your brother and it really
fits with with the together tech yeah
sort of a gestational form of together
tack it's also like it'll bring people
to the game be space that have projects
they don't know yet know about game be
just like do we need more people with
projects and can be yeah but also like
which is the idea of all the YouTube
channels is it's not about getting the
audience it's about this interruption
and then also the interaction of the
audience right like is it not in a I'm
almost at 10,000 subscribers please
subscribe to me but like in a hey we're
almost at 10,000 subscribers and what is
that interaction look like and what does
that people are finding people from
their project because it's growing right
that they obviously I haven't followed
that path that idea cafe where I was
having outreach to people with more
influence to say hey come beyond India
Cafe which although I kind of knew they
weren't going to brought other people
from their channel right because it's
like it well if you search for the
person I'm reaching out for I'm one of
the ones that I come up I might actually
continue doing that that I be the way to
continue but no idea cafe is kind of
focused on gaming it's just that's what
I'm totally open to doing the ones on
mental health and disability and
queerness and everything else I was
doing them on before as well but the
slot that is consistently there is idea
cafe and that yes to have people bring
their influence and also share influence
right like if whatever channel we're
hosting it on becomes popular because
for people want to know about projects
and they want to showcase theirs and
just being on it gives you a boost and
also it brings like it's just a good
marketing strategy for us as whatever
channel that is and anyone who comes on
there right without needing to put money
into it that's also with the idea of
cafe it was like asking people who are
already on social media come participate
and bring your whatever one fall over
zero followers and also like I linked
back to them I haven't been doing that
with game B people because it's good
exit a little early today actually baby
right now
if that's possible but I think we're a
good space of a little doctors thing I
ought to take care of all right before a
the only thing is to our next meeting
but I think we can do that on Facebook
it'll be the whatever the first um
Friday is in the new year I just don't
know exactly what day that is which I
believe means we're taking off two weeks
no one weeks off and then so the 27th is
off and then yet we're back the next
sounds great all right
like sometimes though all right thank
you bye YouTube